One Night Changes Everything
A Cinderella Christmas is a romance, comedy, tv
movie film directed by Tosca Musk.
Angie works hard to run her uncle’s events business
while her cousin Candace takes the credit.
When Angie takes a night off to have fun at the Christmasquerade Ball, the mask and gown allow her
to let loose, and she quickly catches the eye of Nicholas, a wealthy local bachelor.
But then Angie has to go before revealing her identity, leaving Nicholas searching
for his mystery woman in this modern take on the classic fairy tale.
Angie Wells, played by Emma Rigby.
Nikolaus Karmichael, played by Peter Porte.
Candace Karilla, played by Sarah Stouffer.
Max, played by Leland B. Martin.
Victoria Carmichael, played by Lesley-Anne Down.
Otto Karilla, played by Michael Dempsey.
A Cinderella Story is an American anthology series of films created by
Leigh Dunlap and based on the Cinderella fairytale.
The film series is owned and distributed by Warner Bros..
Although the first film was theatrically released, all
the remaining films were direct-to-video.
The film explores themes of marriage proposal, secret identity,
female protagonist, woman director, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.